Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 4: Supplemental Files, 1971-2008
  - Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 1976-2008
    - Subseries 5: Reel to Reel, 1976-1991
      - DeConcini ECN Original CR 4,5. December 23, 1989 (Box 524)
      - Radio Report (unedited). January 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (unedited). February 20, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (unedited). May 16, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (uncut). June 18, 1990 (Box 525)
      - DeConcini Q&A. July 17, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report. September 10, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (uncut). October 9, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (uncut). November 13, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (edited). November 13, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (edited). December 12, 1990 (Box 525)
      - Senator Dennis DeConcini (edited). January 17, 1991 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (edited). March 22, 1991 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report. August 19, 1991 (Box 525)
      - Radio Report (edited). October 9, 1991 (Box 525)
  - Series 3: Memorabilia, 1971-1995
    - Subseries 1: Albums, 1977-1994
      - Memorabilia: Albums. 1977-1994 (Box 526)
    - Subseries 2: Memorabilia, 1978-1992
      - Memorabilia: Memorabilia, Campaign Banners. no date (Box 527)
      - Memorabilia: Memorabilia, Campaign Buttons. 1978-1992 (Box 527)
      - Memorabilia: Memorabilia, Congressional License Plates. 1985 (Box 527)
      - Memorabilia: Memorabilia, Name Plate. 1983 (Box 527)
      - Memorabilia: Memorabilia, Personalized Mug. no date (Box 527)
      - Memorabilia: Memorabilia, Rubber Stamps. no date (Box 527)
    - Subseries 3: Plaques, 1975-1995
      - Memorabilia: Plaques. no date (Box 528)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques. no date, 1975-1982 (Box 529)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques. 1982-1988 (Box 530)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques. 1988-1991 (Box 531)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques. 1992-1994 (Box 532)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques. 1994-1995 (Box 533)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques, Oversize. no date (Box 534)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques, Oversize. 1982-1987 (Box 535)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques, Oversize. 1988-1990 (Box 536)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques, Oversize. 1990-1993 (Box 537)
      - Memorabilia: Plaques, Oversize. 1994-1995 (Box 538)
    - Subseries 4: Prints, 1971-1994
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Law Commemorative- Signed by Ronald Reagan (4). 1984-1988 (Box 539)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Bumper Sticker (1). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Capital Hill (2). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Constitution (2). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Constitutional Series (7). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Dennis DeConcini- Portrait (2). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Donkey (1). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Drawing by Child (2). no date, 1978 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Legislative Act (15). 1980-1988 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Legislative Proclamation (5). 1978-1979 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Legislative Resolution (3). 1985-1993 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Legislative Record (3). 1986-1994 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Native American (1). no date (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Newspaper Clipping (3). 1976-1995 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Pre-congressional Endorsement Letter. 1976 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Political Cartoons (15). 1978-1979 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Wedding Announcement (1). 1988 (Box 540)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Oversize-Legislative Act. 1992 (Box 541)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Oversize- Desert. 1982 (Box 542)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Israel. no date (Box 543)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Israeli Coin. 1971 (Box 543)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Israeli Peace Medal Award. 1994 (Box 543)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Legislative Act (3). 1978-1988 (Box 544)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Political Poster- Bradley, Bill. 1984 (Box 545)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Air Force. 1992 (Box 546)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, Senate Membership. 1977 (Box 546)
      - Memorabilia: Prints, United States Customs. 1989 (Box 546)
    - Subseries 5: Paintings, 1976-1992
      - Memorabilia: Paintings, DDC. 1976 (Box 547)
      - Memorabilia: Paintings, DDC. no date (Box 548)
      - Memorabilia: Paintings, Sand art. no date (Box 548)
      - Memorabilia: Paintings, Ukraine School. 1992 (Box 548)
    - Subseries 6: Objects, 1981-1994
      - Blue velvet box containing small silver plate with etchings-from Al Hilal Club. no date (Box 549)
      - Glass award, engraved-from Chiih To Industries. 1992 (Box 549)
      - Glass plate with picture of mine and miners-Phelps Dodge Mining Centennial in Arizona ward. 1981 (Box 549)
      - Metal etching with wood backing of Native American drummers. no date (Box 549)
      - Shadow box, small-contains two patches and a pin- from 82D Airborne Division Troopers Award. 1981 (Box 549)
      - Silver and gold metal object with Hebrew letter in plastic display box-Community Service Award, from Chabab Lubavitch of Arizona. 1993 (Box 549)
      - Blue and white flag, small-Ashdad, with small gold pin. no date (Box 550)
      - Brown box containing Republic of China flag and small card with paper fans and characters. no date (Box 550)
      - Fabric, multi-color- from Samarhand Mayor, Uzbekistan. no date (Box 550)
      - Green Velvet box containing maroon and gold fabric. no date (Box 550)
      - Yarmulke, Crocheted-black with white letter letters spelling Dennis. no date (Box 550)
      - Concrete pieces, from Berlin Wall (2). no date (Box 551)
      - Concrete/Stone doorstop with metal, engraved piece, from Operation Catacomb Douglas Tunnel. 1990 (Box 551)
      - Ironwood carved into shape of Roadrunners (2). no date (Box 551)
      - Metal bookends in shape of eagle, 1776 on front (2). no date (Box 551)
      - Framed object with blue velvet, copper Star of David, and engraving-Henry M. Jackson Leadership Award- from Union of Councils for Soviet Jews. 1989 (Box 552)
      - Metal fire chief hat, small, with wood stand-Honorary Fire Chief Award, Congressional Fire Services Caucus, from Volunteer Firemen's Insurance. no date (Box 552)
      - Silver bowl, large-Award from Federal Bureau of Prisons. 1994 (Box 552)
      - Small white box containing leather belt buckle with wildcat-U.S. Army ROTC. no date (Box 552)
      - Wood flag display box containing United States flag, from George J. Weise. no date (Box 553)
      - Shadow Box, large, contains menorah-Henry M. Jackson Senatorial Leadership Award- presented by Jewish Community Relations Council of New York. 1993 (Box 554)
      - Wood carving, large-The Birthplace of a Free Democratic Angola, UNITA. 1989 (Box 555)
      - Fiberglass, painted seal, large-Federal Law Enforcement Training Center. no date (Box 556)
      - Fiberglass, painted seal, large-United States of America Federal Election Commission. no date (Box 556)
      - Fiberglass, painted seal, large-Treasury U.S. Customs Service. no date (Box 556)
      - Metal seal mounted on wood, small-Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms. no date (Box 556)
      - Metal seal mounted on wood, large-Great Seal of the State of Arizona 1912. no date (Box 556)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-United States Federal Labor Relations Authority. no date (Box 556)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-Executive Office of the President of the United States Office of Administration. no date (Box 557)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-General Services Administration. no date (Box 557)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-National Archives and Records Administration. no date (Box 557)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-United States Office of Personnel Management. no date (Box 557)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-United States Secret Service Department of the Treasury. no date (Box 557)
      - Plastic, painted seal, large-U.S. Merit Systems Protection Board 1883. no date (Box 557)
  - Series 4: Oversize, 1972-1994
    - Subseries 1: Biographical Files, 1972-1994
      - Awards, Certificates, and Recognition. 1972-1994 (Box 558, Folder 1)
    - Subseries 2: Photographs, 1978-1988
      - 100th Congress. no date (Box 559, Folder 1)
      - Carter, Jimmy. 1978 (Box 559, Folder 2)
      - DeConcini, Dennis. no date (Box 559, Folder 3)
      - Halley's Comet. no date (Box 559, Folder 4)
      - Helsinki Commission. 1988 (Box 559, Folder 5)
      - Lowell Observatory- Flagstaff, Arizona. no date (Box 559, Folder 6)
      - Democratic National Convention. 1984 (Box 559, Folder 7)
      - New York City Police Pipe Band. no date (Box 559, Folder 8)
      - SALT River Project. no date (Box 559, Folder 9)
      - Staats, Elmer B. no date (Box 559, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified. no date (Box 559, Folder 11)
      - U.S. Customs Service Aircraft. no date (Box 559, Folder 12)
      - Von Raab, William. no date (Box 559, Folder 13)
      - Weise, George. no date (Box 559, Folder 14)
      - Woolsey, R. James. no date (Box 559, Folder 15)
  - Series 5: Restricted Material, Restricted until January, 2044
    - Restricted Material. (Box 560-611)
  - Series 6: Presidential Letters and Pens, 1978-1994
    - Carter, Jimmy, regarding the singing of the Bankruptcy Reform Act into law, November 12, 1978 (Box 612, Frame 1)
  - Carter, Jimmy, regarding the singing of the Federal Magistrate Act of 1979 into law, October 22, 1979 (Box 612, Frame 2)
  - Carter,Jimmy, regarding the singing of the Customs Courts Act of 1980 into law, November 10, 1980 (Box 612, Frame 3)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding proclamation of National P.O.W.-M.I.A. Recognition Day, October 2, 1981 (Box 612, Frame 4)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding the extension of the Voting Rights Act of 1965, June 30, 1982 (Box 613, Frame 1)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding H.R. 4364 giving additional land to the Pascua Yaqui Tribe, January 5, 1983 (Box 613, Frame 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding proclamation of Helsinki Human Rights Day, July 27, 1983 (Box 613, Frame 3)
  - Ronald, regarding Senate Joint Resolution 46, commemorating the 75th anniversary of Arizona statehood, April 24, 1987 (Box 613, Frame 4)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding Senate Joint Resolution 58, designating April, 1987 as Child Abuse Prevention Month, July 23, 1987 (Box 614, Frame 1)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding Senate Joint Resolution 57, designating May 3-10, 1987 as National Older Americans Abuse Prevention Week, July 27, 1987 (Box 614, Frame 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding S.942 preventing immediate wage reductions for blue collar Federal workers in the Tucson area, July 30, 1987 (Box 614, Frame 3)
  - Reagan, Ronald, regarding the approval of H.R. 5210, The Anti-Drug Abuse Act of 1988, December 5, 1988 (Box 614, Frame 4)
  - Clinton, Bill, regarding signing into law H.R. 1723, The Central Intelligence Agency Voluntary Separation Pay Act, June, June 9, 1993 (Box 614, Frame 5)
  - Clinton, Bill, regarding passage of the Crime Bill, September 13, 1994 (Box 614, Frame 6)
  - Clinton, Bill, regarding passage of the 1995 Treasury Postal Appropriations Act, October 4, 1994 (Box 614, Frame 7)
  - Addendum, 1996-2008
    The materials contained in this addendum are videotapes with interviews and guest appearances featuring Dennis DeConcini throughout various stages in his political career. DeConcini donated the additional materials in January 2012.
  - 1 CNBC, Upfront Tonight with Diane Dimond and Geraldo Rivera, Dennis DeConcini. February 6, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 2 Ellis Island Medals of Honor. May 19, 1996 (Box 615)
  - 3 FINCA International Inc., FINCA Village Banking, Maksuda’s Story Kyrgyzstan, and Gertrude’s Story Uganda. no date (Box 615)
  - 4 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini. October 5, 2002 (Box 615)
  - 5 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini. September 14, 2004 (Box 615)
  - 6 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini-Daytime. December 11, 2003 (Box 615)
  - 7 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini-Daytime. February 9, 2004 (Box 615)
  - 8 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Al D’Amato. December 15, 2000 (Box 615)
  - 9 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Al D’Amato. July 27, 2001 (Box 615)
  - 10 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Al D’Amato. October 29, 2002 (Box 615)
  - 11 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Bill Brock. January 28, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 12 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Chris Henick. April 22, 2004 (Box 615)
  - 13 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Clinton on Trial. January 30, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 14 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Frank Fahrenkopf. December 22, 2004 (Box 615)
  - 15 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Larry Pressler. February 13, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 16 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Larry Pressler. April 10, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 17 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Larry Pressler. April 18, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 18 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Newt Gingrich. November 8, 2008 (Box 615)
  - 19 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Senator Frank Murkowski. October 2000 (Box 615)
  - 20 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini and Senator George Voinovich. October 17, 2000 (Box 615)
  - 21 Fox News, Dennis DeConcini with Cliff May RNC and Remarks on Al Gore. February 3, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 22 Fox News, Newt Gingrich. December 21, 2000 (Box 615)
  - 23 Fox News, Newt Gingrich. January 11, 2001 (Box 615)
  - 24 Fox News, Re Conduct. August 2, 2001 (Box 615)
  - 25 Fox News. February 11, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 26 Fox News. December 19, 2003 (Box 615)
  - 27 Fox News. September 29, 2004 (Box 615)
  - 28 Fox News, The Edge, Dennis DeConcini and Wayne Allard. November 21, 2000 (Box 615)
  - 29 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. February 9, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 30 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. January 30, 2002 (Box 615)
  - 31 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. November 1, 2002 (Box 615)
  - 32 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. December 2, 2002 (Box 615)
  - 33 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. January 15, 2003 (Box 615)
  - 34 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. October 10, 2003 (Box 615)
  - 35 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini. March 23, 2004 (Box 615)
  - 36 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini and Bob Dornan. April 22, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 37 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini and Chris Cannon. May 18, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 38 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini and JD Hayworth. April 29, 1999 (Box 615)
  - 1 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini and Pete Wilson. August 16, 2001 (Box 616)
  - 2 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini, Robert Andrews, and Bill Frist. November 20, 2000 (Box 616)
  - 3 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Dennis DeConcini with Governor Thompson. October 31, 2000 (Box 616)
  - 4 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes, Frank Keating. November 14, 2000 (Box 616)
  - 5 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes. April, 15, 1998 (Box 616)
  - 6 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes. February 9, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 7 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes. August 7, 2000 (Box 616)
  - 8 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes. November 30, 2000 (Box 616)
  - 9 Fox News, Hannity and Colmes. December 23, 2002 (Box 616)
  - 10 Fox News, On the Record, Dennis DeConcini. October 4, 2002 (Box 616)
  - 11 Fox News, War Zone with Geraldo Rivera, Dennis DeConcini, Bob Graham, and Mark Kirk. June 23, 2002 (Box 616)
  - 12 Fox News Cable, Dennis DeConcini and Bill Brock. February, 17, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 13 Fox News Cable, Dennis DeConcini and Thomas Ewing. March 4, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 14 Fox News Live, Dennis DeConcini. June 17, 2004 (Box 616)
  - 15 Fox News Live, Dennis DeConcini. February 15, 2005 (Box 616)
  - 16 Fox News Live, Dennis DeConcini, Mike DeWine, and Al Gore. March 6, 2000 (Box 616)
  - 17 Fox News Live, Dennis DeConcini, Mike DeWine, and Al Gore Election-Night of Ohio Primary. March 2000 (Box 616)
  - 18 Good Morning America, International Child Abduction. no date (Box 616)
  - 19 Heute Journal, Report about the Rosewood Story. January 18, 1999 [German] (Box 616)
  - 20 John Walsh’s Introduction Speech for the 15th Anniversary Board Dinner. June 17, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 21 Left Behind by: Christof Putzel. April 2002 (Box 616)
  - 22 Mafia Marriage and Linda Skladany. no date (Box 616)
  - 23 MSNBC, Hardball with Chris Matthews, Segments with Dennis DeConcini. January 16, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 24 MSNBC, Senator Dennis DeConcini. February 4, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 25 National Center for Missing and Exploited Children, Megan’s Law and the Protection of Children in the Online Age-American Criminal Law Review. April 15, 1998 (Box 616)
  - 26 National Training Center, Fishing for the Future: The Lake Havasu Fisheries Improvement Program. no date (Box 616)
  - 27 NEWS Segments, Missing Persons Week, Dennis DeConcini Speaks as a Guest from the International Missing Persons Centre. February, 8, 1999 (Box 616)
  - 28 Nyumbani CBS Interview. December 2001 (Box 616)
  - 29 One-On-One with John McLaughlin, Father Dag Interview. June 2002 (Box 616)
  - 30 Pat Summerall Productions, Champions of Industry, National Center for Missing and Exploited Children. no date (Box 616)
  - 31 Spotlight Video, Nyumbani. 1998 (Box 616)
  - 32 The University of Arizona College of Law [Ares Auditorium], The Impeachment Trial of Abraham Lincoln. no date (Box 616)